red-sun-design.com 2018-11-18

# red sun design - Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. This page explains what happens to your personal information that we collect through this website.

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.red-sun-design.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

If you use the contact form for pre-sale and general questions, we collect the following personal information entered in the form:

  * Name
  * Email address

This information will be used by us for the sole purpose of answering your questions.

We keep the contact form submissions for  six months, in case there are follow-up questions. We will not share the information submitted through the contact form without your consent. We do not use the information submitted through the contact form for marketing purposes.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, which is a tool that measures how users interact with website content. As a user navigates between web pages, Google Analytics records information about the page a user has seen, for example the URL of the page.

Google Analytics uses cookies that allow an analysis of the use of the website. The information generated is transmitted to a Google server and stored there. You can prevent this by setting up your browser so that no cookies are stored.

For more information on how Google Analytics uses cookies, see Google’s Cookie Usage guide: https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage.

More information about how Google Analytics handles user data can be found in Google’s privacy policy: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245

### Social Sharing Buttons

This website includes facebook and twitter sharing buttons. No data will be transmitted to those social networks unless you click one of the sharing buttons.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

If you use the contact form for pre-sale and general questions, we keep the contact form submissions for  six months, in case there are follow-up questions.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
